(Number 1 luxury boulevard in Korea)
I come to this neighborhood when I have errands to run.
I used to come here very often.
I used to go to a salon on this alley when I first debuted.
- That's why you came here often.
- And...
I used to walk around this block all the time.
- I see.
- Okay.
Did you get a matching drink to your shirt?
No.
(He's drinking a yellow tea in his yellow T-shirt.)
The air this morning...
- felt slightly cool.
- Yes.
I thought I could get a warm cup of tea.
(The weather calls for a warm cup of tea.)
I'm getting a feeling that Yoo Hai Jin is joining us.
His movie will be released soon.
- No? Oh, you heard who it was.
- According to the intel I got,
he and I worked on a project together.
I heard that my former colleague was going to join us today.
So you know who's coming today.
- Right. Should I tell you?
- I see.
Who is it?
He was in this movie.
- "Tazza?"
- Yes.
Is it Jeong Min from the movie?
- That was the previous season.
- Okay.
- The one with Byun Yo Han.
- I see. He's joining us today.
And Roh Jae Won.
- I see.
- Yes. I'm correct, right?
(Chuckling)
- What is it?
- Why did you...
- I can totally read your cards.
- Why do you want...
- to keep it a secret?
- I can totally read their cards...
- about the guests.
- Why keep it a secret?
- Exactly. Right now...
- I just don't get it.
Have you met Jae Seok?
We performed together in a dance group.
(They're walking in the rain.)
(Are they the lead actors from "Tazza?")
- Really?
- He's my former member.
- Yes.
- I think they're coming.
- Yes, they're coming.
They're super quiet.
- My gosh.
- Hello.
- What?
Hello. It's been a while.
- Where did you get your intel?
- What?
(Young K of DAY6?)
- What? Hold on.
- It's Yoo Seung Ho.
You...
Hello.
- You thought... It's Seung Ho.
- I thought I read their move.
Was I wrong?
- Today...
- Are they coming next week?
- Wait.
- You said Byun Yo Han was coming.
It's a mess.
- It's been a while, Seung Ho.
- It must be for another week.
- It's been a while.
- Hey, K.
- Yes.
- What...
- Let's sit down.
- Okay.
Hello.
What was that all about?
- I heard...
- You were all cocky.
I was totally being a snob.
Why did you act like a know-it-all?
My gosh, come on.
They never tell us who's joining us for that week.
- Right. I heard it was a secret.
- We're always in the dark.
But he told me that Byun Yo Han and Roh Jae Won were joining us.
I was just thinking about the movies that would hit the theaters soon.
And I got this secret intel that they would join us.
- I...
- Where did you get this bad intel?
(He ruined the opening segment with his bad intel.)
- That's what I thought.
- So I was boasting about that.
- My gosh. Come on.
- This is a mess.
- Hey, K.
- Yes.
- My gosh.
- Hold on. How do you guys...
- Nice to meet you.
know each other?
- We're the same age.
- Yes.
- I see.
- We're the same age.
(With his cute looks and exceptional acting, )
(this little kid was beloved by the whole country.)
(And this is how the little kid turned out.)
(The spine-chilling psychopath in "Flex x Cop 2.")
(Whether it's playing a villain, )
(acting in a period drama, )
(or depicting a romantic character, he always delivers.)
(The actor we were dying to invite to our show)
(Actor Yoo Seung Ho)
(A representative band in Korea, DAY6)
(In their 9th year, their sleeper-hit legend began.)
("DAY6 Sells Out All Tickets to Their Year-End Concert")
("DAY6 Sells Out 6 Solo Concerts in a Row")
(A continuous streak of sold-out shows)
(He's the bassist and vocalist of DAY6.)
(And he also made it as a solo artist.)
(Young K of DAY6)
(And these two...)
(showed off their friendship at an awards ceremony.)
(Hugging)
(The two same-age friends with a strong friendship)
- We're the same age.
I starred in DAY6's music video a long time ago.
That's how we became friends.
- Really?
- Yes.
- So...
- Welcome to the show - Show
He was the lead actor of that music video.
- Seung Ho was?
- Yes.
Right.
- I didn't know.
- Yes.
He saved our song.
Then you guys aren't here today...
to promote any new projects? You came here just as friends?
As for me, I already finished filming the drama.
It's airing on SBS now. It's called "Flex x Cop 2."
- "Flex x Cop 2."
- Yes.
- With Bo Hyun.
- Right.
- With Ahn Bo Hyun.
- It's airing now.
- We finished filming the drama.
- Right.
- That's it.
- Then you have nothing to promote.
I'm here just as his friend.
- As Seung Ho's friend.
(Young Hyun is here as Seung Ho's friend.)
DAY6 isn't going to release any new songs?
I just finished performing as a solo artist.
People with finished projects are here.
- You guys are here as friends.
- Yes.
You guys are on our show to have fun together...
- as friends.
- Yes.
(This is a social visit.)
Do you guys have any ties to this neighborhood?
- I was going to school in Canada.
- Yes.
Then I signed with JYP. And their office used to be here.
Right. It was around the corner.
- Yes.
- Over there.
So I was in this neighborhood when I was a trainee.
I went to Chungdam High School.
- You went to Chungdam High School.
- Yes.
(Young K has memories of his trainee days here.)
I lived here for a long time.
What about you, Seung Ho? Any ties here?
I don't know anything about this neighborhood.
- You don't?
- No.
Isn't your salon here or something?
Right. I come here for the salon or for work.
Other than that, I rarely come to Seoul.
Then where do you usually spend your time?
- I live in Gyeonggi Province.
- I see.
I don't come to Seoul unless I have work.
It's so true. He only comes to Seoul for work.
We talked about meeting up for a very long time.
- We talked about meeting up.
- Right.
But you're busy.
Right. But...
- you...
- He's too busy.
- I...
- He's...
- Why did you bring this up?
- I mean...
So when I'm lucky enough...
to get a call from him during his break,
I would be busy with work.
- Our schedules were off.
- I see.
We'd video call, though.
- It's the same with everyone.
- Yes.
- When he has concerts, - It's the same.
he always invites me.
He came to my solo concert too.
- Your friendship runs deep.
- Yes.
We don't have to spell it out,
- Right.
- but we feel connected.
I'm getting a feeling that once we get older,
- we'd see each other more often.
- I see.
- When you guys have more time?
- Yes.
- I love DAY6's songs.
- Thank you.
I held a fan-meet in South America.
I sang your song, "You Were Beautiful."
But I changed the lyrics, "beautiful" to "bonita."
Bonita
- I changed the lyrics and sang it.
- That's awesome.
No way.
(Screaming)
(He won over the hearts of his fans with DAY6's song.)
- No way.
- I'm serious.
- What?
- You did all kinds of things.
- Seriously.
- Bonita - Yes.
The syllables of the lyrics...
- They matched.
- They worked out.
Could we do the same thing?
- Go ahead.
- Yes.
- If you're ever in South America...
- Do it.
- or in Spanish-speaking countries, - Yes.
change the lyrics to bonita. They'd love it.
- I'll copy your act then.
- Sure.
You know what? I mean, Young K also looks young.
But Seung Ho doesn't seem to age at all.
- You don't get old.
- He doesn't.
- You don't.
- What are you talking about? No.
- I...
- That's enough.
Seriously. Young K...
I should say that to you about your good looks.
No. You already look so young.
Both of you. That's enough.
(Going quiet)
- Both of you. That's enough.
- Okay.
(Feeling uneasy)
It's way too early for this.
I look awful this morning.
Anyway, let's check where we're headed today.
Okay. Let's go. Here's our first Whenever Guest.
"Yang Mi Ri."
- "Mi Ri?"
- Yes.
"In Cheongdam-dong,"
"there's a magic spell for Cinderella makeovers."
- "With one brushstroke,"
- "One brushstroke."
"they can transform into Byeon Woo Seok or KARINA."
"To make their special day shine even more,"
"I add highlight to their faces."
"I'd love to give a magic spell to my spare time too."
I think she might be a makeup artist.
- There are many beauty salons here.
- There are a lot of salons here.
- That's the vibe I'm getting.
- Yes.
- We can easily find stylists here.
We'll be there in ten minutes on foot.
- Let's get going.
- Yes.
- Shall we?
- Let's cross the street.
(They set out while humming "bonita.")
The song became "Bonita."
Why don't we cross the street?
Or should we walk a little bit?
I feel uncomfortable to film in this neighborhood.
- I know a lot of people here.
- Exactly.
- Let's cross.
- Right?
My styling team is...
- right around the corner.
- Exactly.
- Their office is here?
- Yes.
I'm going to get text messages from my friends.
- "What are you doing?"
- "Jae Seok."
"What are you doing today?"
This neighborhood has a lot of great restaurants.
- This alley has a ton of them.
- So many of them are here.
Right.
There used to be a great diner in this block.
- Right. That's...
- Is it still here?
- Was it Cheongdam Valley?
- Yes.
- I know Cheongdam Valley.
- You do?
- Of course.
How come I'm the only one who doesn't?
- It's right there.
- It's still here.
- Cheongdam Valley is here.
They serve diner-style food.
- They serve diner-style food.
- They're famous for their fish.
(A famous diner in Cheongdam-dong)
- It's been here forever.
- It has.
- It was here when I first debuted.
- Cheongdam Valley.
- My manager took me there for food.
- That restaurant...
- opened until late night.
- That's right.
- I used to eat there late at night.
- The restaurant is still running.
Don't you eat at a restaurant after visiting the beauty salon?
What? No.
I might've eaten there too. Have I?
Seung Ho hasn't eaten there.
No, I haven't.
I'm sure your manager took you there.
Right. They serve diner-style meals.
- Like grilled fish and so on.
- Right.
- This restaurant...
- You get a full meal.
- They open early in the morning.
- Right.
- Young Hyun, when JYP had...
- Yes.
- offices in this neighborhood, - Yes.
there were good restaurants nearby.
There was a ton of restaurants.
- We...
- Right?
You've been here long enough...
if you know the restaurant called Grill and Neobi.
(Happy to hear the name)
- Grill and Neobi.
- Yes.
- I know the one.
- What?
Then we used to eat at Alley Restaurant.
- Alley Restaurant.
- Yes.
I was having a meal there and got scolded.
- Why?
- They said...
rice was unlimited.
I didn't know any better and I pigged it out.
Young Hyun eats a lot.
His portion is crazy big.
I ordered one bowl of doenjang stew,
but I ate eight bowls of rice.
(He ate 8 bowls of rice.)
They didn't know you'd eat that much rice.
(He was that hungry when he was a trainee.)
Seung Ho, what about you? Are you a big eater too?
I...
- I thought I was.
- Okay.
After watching him eat,
I realized I was a light eater.
My gosh. Young Hyun is considered a big eater...
even among big eaters.
- I know.
- Be honest. You can finish...
two bags of ramyeon in no time.
Two bags? No, four.
- Four?
- Seriously.
He's amazing.
- I ate ramyeon 3 days ago.
- I can eat 2 bags of ramyeon.
- I can't eat more than 2 bags.
- Me too. I can eat up to 2 bags.
- Two bags.
- It was just three days ago.
I added four bags of ramyeon noodles to budae stew.
Four bags of ramyeon noodles to budae stew?
Four bags of noodles?
(The class of a big eater)
- All by yourself?
- Yes.
Did you also eat rice?
Where does all that food go?
- That's interesting.
- That's why I rarely eat.
- Really?
- Yes.
I need to watch my diet.
I'm always hungry.
The prices are quite steep at this restaurant.
But how about Wolfgang's Steakhouse for lunch?
It's way too expensive.
- It's right here.
- Well, only one of us...
- will have to pay.
- Right.
Sounds good.
- Oh, my.
- Wolfgang's Steakhouse.
I've only heard about this steakhouse.
- Really?
- I've never been there.
- It's right here.
- Never.
- Seung Ho.
- Yes.
- You've only heard about it?
My gosh, Seung Ho.
What am I going to do with him?
The lunch bill will come out to 1,000 dollars, I guess.
I've only eaten there once.
- Just once?
- Someone else was paying.
I've eaten there only once too.
(They're getting close to their destination.)
There are so many good restaurants. It will be hard to pick.
The show is completely unscripted.
Right here. If we go straight down, it's the beauty salon I go to.
All the salons are here.
It's the second building here.
Now that we're here today, he's talking about his beauty salon.
Right there. It's down the street.
(Feeling excited by the familiar alley)
It's right here. It's that building.
- Where?
- This one.
- Oh, this building?
- It says "hair and makeup."
It has to be.
- Hold on. Is it the basement?
- I think it's the basement.
The cafe... Wait. That one also says "hair and makeup."
She's smiling at us.
(Several beauty salons are in the building.)
- I think it's the basement.
- The cafe...
Let me check the floor number.
- She's smiling at us.
- It's Basement Level One.
- Basement Level One.
- I mean...
- She keeps smiling at us.
- Right.
- Are you Mi Ri?
- I see. A cafe.
You're Mi Ri, right?
- Hello, Mi Ri.
- Hello.
This is a huge salon.
- Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, Mi Ri.
(First Whenever Guest: Yang Mi Ri)
- Isn't it a hair salon?
- Hold on.
- I had a feeling it was you.
- Yes.
- Your name sounded familiar.
- What is it?
Have you two met before?
I was working at a different salon then.
We met there.
- It wasn't here, right?
- It was at a different salon.
(She used to work at a salon that handled JYP artists.)
- When you were working...
- Yes.
- at a different salon?
- Right.
- Let's go inside and talk.
- Great.
I see chairs there.
(Diving into Mi Ri's spare time)
Is this the place?
There are so many hair salons...
and makeup salons in Cheongdam-dong.
(Then the makeup room comes into view.)
(She used to be in charge of dolling up the K-pop artists.)
(She beautifies special moments in our day-to-day lives now.)
(Makeup Artist Yang Mi Ri)
Have you been well?
It's been so long.
My gosh. You look even more handsome.
(Kicking off their first spare time on a good note)
Anyway, this is the beauty salon where you work, Mi Ri.
- Right.
- It's also a hair salon, right?
- Yes.
- How long have you been here?
I've been working at this salon for a year now.
- I see.
- Yes.
She can transform people into Byeon Woo Seok...
- or KARINA with her touch.
- KARINA.
Actually, I included their names in my letter for a reason.
- Why is that?
- It's not that Byeon Woo Seok...
or KARINA come to our salon.
- They don't come here.
- I see.
- Unfortunately, they don't.
- Wait.
- It'd be great if they did.
- That would be amazing.
- Okay.
- There's a famous beauty salon...
- Yes.
on an upper floor of this building.
They go to that famous salon upstairs.
- The salon upstairs?
- They go to the one upstairs.
They get their hair and makeup done at the salon upstairs.
- They're very popular.
- Right. Yes, they are.
- So their fans...
- Do they come here?
- No. They go to the salon upstairs.
- I see.
- They go to the salon upstairs.
- Upstairs?
- They go there.
- I see.
When they can't book a reservation with the salon,
- they come here instead.
- I see.
- They come here instead.
- It's the trickle-down effect.
- It's an economic term.
- Yes.
So I do their makeup here.
- I transform them into...
- So...
Byeon Woo Seok or KARINA.
They get their hair and makeup done at the salon upstairs.
- That's right.
- But she can offer...
the same service.
- That's right.
- Yes.
When the salon upstairs is fully booked,
- they can come to you instead.
- Right.
- That's your point, right?
- Of course.
We can also provide the same service.
She also polished up my looks and turned me into Young K of DAY6.
Of course.
I can totally transform them into DAY6.
- Everything is possible.
- Of course.
All right. Usually, when there are two beauty salons...
- in the same building, - Right?
I'd worry about the competition.
Since your salon opened after them, I thought you might have concerns.
Gosh, not at all.
"No."
- My salon gets...
- Okay.
a lot of desperate people.
- What do you mean by desperate?
- Like people going to auditions.
- People going to auditions.
- I see.
Or people going on blind dates.
They must be really desperate.
- Of course.
- So they want to make...
- a good impression.
- Yes.
Because my clients are desperate,
I'm also desperate.
- I want to do a good job.
- Well...
What kind of request do you get from women going on blind dates?
They want to highlight their natural image...
without giving off the salon vibe,
- so men don't spot it.
- So it's not too much.
They don't want it to be too much.
- They want the effortless look.
- That's important.
Looking good effortlessly is important for blind dates.
- That's it.
- Looking good effortlessly.
They have to look good effortlessly,
but it has to look different in a subtle manner.
- Yes, it has to.
- Right.
That kind of makeup might take longer time.
So it has to look like they did the makeup,
but it should look like they're very good at makeup.
"Their makeup looks flawless."
- Something like that.
- "Their makeup is so stylish."
Right. "She knows how to make herself look good."
That's the vibe we're going for.
- Do you also get men as clients?
- Of course.
How do you do their makeup then?
As for men, if their makeup is excessive,
- It would show then.
- it shows.
I focus on making their skin look...
clean and neat. I try to bring out a clean-cut vibe...
from men.
Then she specializes in making people look good effortlessly.
Why don't you change the name to Looking Good Effortlessly?
But I'm good at full glam looks too.
- I see.
- Full glam looks too?
When do you usually get requests for full glam looks?
I get those requests for people who are going out at night.
(Screaming)
- People going out at night.
- Even when they go out at night?
- I get some clients after 6pm.
- Right.
- Yes.
- I can totally see that.
- They must stand out.
- Yes.
They want to stand out even in dark places.
People who are planning to go to places with heavy lights.
- Those lights are intense.
- With heavy lights...
- So that's one example.
- There should've been...
beauty salons during my clubbing days.
I went clubbing without any makeup on.
I was just sweaty at the clubs.
I bet she's good at giving makeup...
- that suits your image.
- Exactly.
- So I can tell...
- The makeup that suits your image.
- that she's an expert.
- Yes.
I'm sure you get all kinds of clients here.
You must've gotten a client that threw you off.
I wouldn't say I was thrown off. But there were a few clients...
I was determined to give my all for.
- I felt this way only for...
- Yes.
- two of my clients.
They were going to the wedding of their ex-boyfriend.
- What?
- They were attending the wedding.
Both of them...
As soon as they walked in, they said,
"I'm so sorry to tell you this."
"But I have to attend the wedding of my ex-boyfriend."
- How did that happen?
- Right.
Well, asking them what happened didn't feel right.
- That's a sensitive topic.
- Yes.
"Were you monkey branched? Did he ghost you?"
"Just how bad of a jerk are we talking here?"
I would ask questions along this line.
- So the type of breakup...
- I'd ask these questions.
- The intensity of the makeup...
- decides the intensity.
I wanted to know how bad it was when they broke up.
I'd ask if their new boyfriends were good enough to show off...
or if they were going to the wedding with them.
These were the questions I asked.
I change the makeup based on the answers I get.
I want to flip the question here.
Let's say you get a new girlfriend.
And if she asks you to go to her ex's wedding with her...
- Should you go with her?
- The boyfriend...
- If I were in his shoes...
- How should he dress up then?
- For the wedding?
- If I were in his shoes,
- I don't think I could go.
- He...
He has to be completely decked out for the wedding.
He's going there for her revenge.
- To help her take revenge?
- Yes.
- Should he go?
- The boyfriend...
That's infuriating.
Does it mean she's still hung up on the guy?
What about me then? What does that say about me?
She wouldn't share that much.
- What do you think, guys?
- Well,
like she explained,
- if she must attend the wedding...
- Because they're colleagues.
- because they're colleagues, - Right.
I'd go all out after hearing the news.
- Right.
- So she doesn't get hurt.
That's what you'd do?
- I'd dress up to the nines.
- That's it.
- I'd look good effortlessly.
- That's what I thought.
I'd come to this beauty salon.
- They'd go together.
- At the end.
What about you, Seung Ho?
I don't know what the story is.
But whatever it is, I don't think I can go.
Exactly. You and I are on the same page.
I don't think I can go.
How could you let your girlfriend go by herself?
The fact that she wants to go by herself...
- I'd stop her.
- I need to stop her then.
- That's understandable.
- "Don't go."
- "Don't go to the wedding."
- "You don't have to attend it."
- Exactly.
- But...
if it's her colleague's wedding,
and if only she doesn't attend it,
- it would look weird.
- I'd understand it then.
- If that's the case.
- She has no choice but to go.
- If she has no choice...
- It seems we're on the same page.
- Right. No one...
No one would want to go. But...
- not attending the wedding...
- I'm sure she can give...
- an explanation.
- That's possible too.
If she's the only one who skips the wedding,
it would be obvious that she skipped it because of him.
Not to show that, she would have to go.
- "I'm completely fine."
- But here's another possibility.
It might sound like something far off in the future.
But anything could happen between them in the future.
Let's turn the tables around.
Let's say I go to the wedding with her,
so she gets her revenge.
She's so happy, and I'm happy too.
But then we break up...
and I'm getting married.
And she shows up...
- She shows up at the wedding again?
- Why think that far ahead?
Revenge begets revenge.
Why can't you just dress up nicely...
and go to the wedding for her sake?
- I get your point. But...
- We're on the same page.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- The ex-boyfriend...
- If they have no choice...
but to attend the wedding, I'd understand.
- But I wouldn't go if possible.
- Right.
- I don't see any reason to go.
- I'd talk about that.
- I'd talk to her.
- "You already won. You have me."
- You and I think alike. Yes.
- Gosh, yes.
- So...
- I'd try to cheer her up.
- You can afford to say that.
Gosh, no.
- I can't say that.
- No.
If he were my boyfriend, I wouldn't go.
- I wouldn't go then.
- I wouldn't go either.
(He ends the heated debate.)
All right. Let's spice up her day...
- with a little excitement.
- Yes.
Young Hyun and Seung Ho are here.
If we make it to Round Three, we're going to Wolfgang's.
- You will?
- Yes, we will.
Let's go to Wolfgang's Steakhouse if we make it to Round Three.
- Let's do it.
- Yes, let's do it.
- Let me open this up.
- Okay.
- I'm excited.
- Yes.
"I've been running for two weeks."
"It will be a great workout partner for a novice runner."
"A Garmin smartwatch."
"A smartwatch."
(The essential item for runners, Garmin smartwatch)
(A must-have for avid runners)
Did you pick up running lately?
- I picked up running as my hobby.
- Yes.
I'm not in any running crew.
- Have you heard of covert running?
- What's that?
Let's say I go out for a run.
- And you're on your run too.
- Yes.
I would run up behind you and secretly tag along.
- Then I'd run behind him.
- To set your pace to his pace?
Yes. I would do that. So let's say I'm running behind him.
When Young K senses something and turns around to look,
- I'd run away.
- Do you go somewhere else?
Afterward, I'd keep running.
When I spot Yeon Seok running, I'd stay with him then.
I'd keep running behind him.
When he senses my presence and turns around,
I'd run away again.
- That's covert running.
- Mi Ri.
- You do all kinds of activities.
- Why is she doing that?
- She does all kinds of things.
- I've been on covert running.
- I don't have...
- Do you need this watch?
a workout buddy.
You don't know how to go about this...
- when you're on your own.
- Right.
- But I don't get in their way.
- You make sure of that.
I secretly set my pace to other people's.
- This can help you keep your pace.
- I've never heard of this.
- Of course.
- We need to win this for you.
- Thank you.
- She's so funny.
- She's funny.
- I'm grateful for this.
Okay.
(One Shot! Closing)
(Finger flick the bottle cap...)
(and close the lid of a cosmetic product.)
(Round 1: 2 eyeshadow palettes)
(They're given 10 bottle caps.)
(But they only have 30 seconds.)
(It's like Alkkagi.)
Gosh, what's this now?
In the end, it's all about finger flicks.
We need to close it with the bottle caps.
They want us to close the lid.
I think we need to hit it pretty hard.
- Exactly. This game...
- This is...
- I'm not wearing a thimble.
- That was too strong.
That was too strong as well. Hold on.
Yes, we have several.
(Failed 3 times)
That was too weak.
It's not easy.
(They're nervous about the challenging difficulty.)
(Yeon Seok practices.)
(It hit the bottom.)
Hold on. The lid won't close.
I have to flick the bottle cap off. But how? Give it a try.
I just can't do it.
(The bottle cap flew and hit the target!)
- You've got the skill.
- He's a natural.
You're good.
- Did we clear one?
- Hold on.
I can't aim well.
Seung Ho, do you want to try?
(Seung Ho also practices.)
- Is this how you flick it?
- Flick it like this.
- Like this.
- Like this?
Like this, horizontally.
But if you do that, the bottle cap flies to the side.
Exactly. Hey, Seung Ho.
If you flick like that, the bottle cap flies to the side.
- Is this how you flick it?
- Like this.
- May I try?
- Go ahead.
(Getting into position as he was taught)
(Seung Ho stares at Jae Seok.)
Why are you looking at me?
We'd better practice multiple times.
- Use them.
- Practice.
Seung Ho, why'd you look at me?
You rarely play Alkkagi, right?
(Cutting him off cleanly)
Go low.
Go low?
That's...
Even if it hits the bottom of the lid, the lid doesn't close.
It should fly a little. This is too far away.
Yes, it should fly a little.
(The bottle cap keeps flying away.)
Seung Ho, you're not getting any hits.
Is it because of the thimble?
(Breathing in)
- Shall we give it a try?
- Shall we?
- Let's do it.
- Okay.
- Good.
- Flick three each.
- Yes.
- We'll do 2.
- Yes, 2.
- Three each, and two each for us.
- Yes.
Then what about the order? First...
Regard me as a useless card.
No.
- The aim doesn't zero in right now.
- What are you talking about?
- The zero...
- Just try it for now.
Okay, then should I go first?
- Go ahead.
- Seung Ho will go first.
- Go last, Young K.
- I...
- Okay.
- Young K, go last.
- I'll go 2nd.
- Then I'll go 3rd.
- Good.
- First.
- Good luck.
- Second.
Let's do a group cheer.
Let's go! Come, Mi Ri.
- In 1, 2, 3. Go!
- Nice.
- Then...
Let me line them up first.
- Let's do this!
- Good luck!
- Even just one.
- We need to secure the prize.
For sure.
Covert running.
- Call it.
- All right.
- Here I go, okay?
- Okay.
- Here we go.
- Ready.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
Set.
- Nice!
- What?
For real?
(Close 1 more lid, and they'll succeed Round 1.)
You're great at it.
You're a hands-on guy, aren't you?
That was close.
It went slightly to the left.
Just do one.
- Nice!
- What?
Nice!
(Yoo One Shot finished it off!)
- Nice!
- He did it. Are we done?
- Did we succeed?
- Success!
- Nice!
- Good luck!
- Round One, success!
(Round 1 succeeded in 1 go)
- Success.
- This feels great.
- Nice.
- We actually did it.
No more covert running.
(Seung Ho and Yeon Seok's outstanding performance)
- We did it.
- I didn't think it'd be possible.
- Nice.
- Amazing.
I was the useless card!
(He didn't get a try.)
- We actually made it.
- We succeeded.
- Young Hyun. We did it.
- Hold on.
I'm getting goosebumps.
It's just a game, but I'm on cloud nine.
- Yes, no more covert running.
- It ended so quickly.
No more covert running!
A smartwatch that'll end...
covert running.
- Thank you.
- You have a friend now.
- We did it.
- The thing is...
Don't be so happy about it.
No, because...
Due to a weird jinx,
if we succeed in Rounds 1 and 2...
- too quickly, - Yes?
we have the hardest time in Round Three.
- We need to be cautious.
- The game gets difficult.
We shouldn't like it so much.
Now then, Round Two.
Go or stop.
Mi Ri, in 1, 2, 3.
- Go!
- Of course.
- It's a go.
- A go.
- Now then...
- Number two.
- Gosh.
- Oh, my.
"A luxury touch for the hand holding the brush,"
"a Gucci silver bracelet."
(Impressed)
(Amazed)
A Gucci bracelet.
(A high-end bracelet has appeared.)
Open it once you become the owner of this bracelet.
See?
(One of her wrists is empty.)
(Moving in)
- Thank you.
- Nice.
- On both wrists.
- Thank you.
- Goodness.
- Sparkling wrists.
She'll have bracelets on both wrists.
My gosh.
(Round 2)
(The cosmetic products get smaller.)
(Round 1)
(Round 2)
- They are round now.
- They're smaller.
This is...
(2 cushion foundations)
This one is tough.
This one is indeed tough.
It's challenging.
Right? The game did get difficult.
Flick it hard.
Shall we give it a shot?
If you practice too much,
- Your fingers hurt.
- your fingers give out.
Your fingers give out.
Seung Ho goes first.
- Shall I?
- Yes.
He's on a roll today.
Seung Ho did well as the first player.
- You mean that spirit?
- Yes.
Seung Ho did well going first.
(Continuing the momentum, Seung Ho is first again.)
- Call it.
- Show us what you've got.
- I'm going to start.
- Okay.
- Call it.
- He's on his knees.
(Solemn)
- Just 1. Let's close 1.
- Should I go next?
- One is enough.
- Strong players should go first.
Seung Ho is good at the real deal.
Here I go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 2.)
Ready. Set.
(2nd try)
- That was so close.
- All right.
- Oh, no.
- Yeon Shik. Go ahead.
(2nd try)
- Nice. That was close.
- Oh, dear.
- Yes! Nice!
- Nice!
- Oh, no.
- Okay.
- You can do it!
- Just one more.
Okay.
Just one more.
- Just one more.
- Hold on.
- Oh, no.
- Ten seconds left.
- You can do it.
- Slowly.
- Slowly, Young Hyun.
Go slow.
- Just that one.
- Five, four, three...
(Failed)
This won't be easy.
Yeon Seok did a good job.
Yeon Seok should go last.
(Yeon Seok is the only one who succeeded in closing a lid.)
I become impatient.
- We don't have enough time.
- No.
Try it.
You can do it.
(Yeon Seok flicks the bottle cap with his whole body.)
- Nice.
- Finally.
- Should we use our bodies?
- It seems like it.
- I like this technique.
- Right?
- This technique.
- I used my weight.
- Hard.
- Okay.
Using my body is a good strategy.
- The bottle cap should fly hard.
- Good.
Use my...
That's how you do it.
- When punching, don't just punch.
- No.
Use my lower body.
You've got to aim, Young Hyun.
(The type to get ahead of himself)
Remember? You eat four packs of ramyeon in budae stew.
Use my lower body.
- Also use your sense of direction.
- Try it, Seung Ho.
- Is force not enough?
Do I use my body?
(Staggering)
- Keep to your style.
- No, here's what I do.
I put my weight into my body.
- I'll just keep to my style.
- Okay.
Keep to your style.
(Bull's-eye)
Nice.
(Feeling the pain)
I don't know if I can hold a spoon later.
Let's adjust how many we each flick.
We should.
Yeon Shik, flick four.
(Ace Yeon Shik gets 4 bottle caps.)
We'll each do two.
- Two each?
- Yes.
- Six in total?
- Yes, six in total.
We'll succeed now. We will.
We will, Mi Ri.
Fourth try.
- Let's do this.
- I'll go first.
- When you've gotten the hang of it.
- He's got it.
Okay.
(Confidently leading the charge)
Here we go.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 4.)
Ready.
- Ready. Set.
- Let's do this.
(4th try)
That was a bad flick.
I'm losing it.
That was close.
(Two failed in the blink of an eye.)
No, don't get rid of it.
- Nice.
- What?
- Seung Ho! You did it!
(What just happened?)
- Nice.
(Closed all lids with bull's-eyes in a row)
- What?
- Seung Ho! You did it!
- You did it, Seung Ho!
- What?
- Unbelievable!
- You did it!
You're good at the real deal.
- Goodness.
- My gosh. Success!
(They succeeded Round 2.)
You each flicked twice. I didn't even go.
- Gosh.
- Incredible.
- You did all the work.
- My gosh.
- Seung Ho.
- I wanted her to have the bracelet.
Amazing.
- Unbelievable.
- Seung Ho is incredible.
- He's the ace.
- We've got an ace right here.
- Seung Ho should flick three.
- For sure.
- Jae Seok, don't cut back.
- Flick more.
Three and three.
- Two and two.
- Okay.
As of the order,
first, second, third, and fourth.
- She hasn't decided yet.
- Right.
Mi Ri hasn't decided yet.
It's a go to the next round.
- Is it a go?
- Yes.
- Nice.
- Go.
- It's a go.
Check the present first.
(Ta-da)
What could be the Round Three present?
"A special healing experience for me, who has been making..."
"someone else's special days,"
"a Park Hyatt stay and spa voucher."
- A stay and spa?
- My gosh.
- What a splendid course.
- A staycation.
Park Hyatt after a run with the bracelet on.
(A staycation after a run with the bracelet on)
- Okay.
- My gosh.
(Luxury healing full course, a hotel stay and spa voucher)
(Round 3)
(There are more cushion foundations.)
- The number?
- This is bad. It won't be easy.
Is it three?
It's tough.
(3 cushion foundations)
Three?
The number?
I expected the targets to get smaller.
It's better than that.
- It's...
- Having more is better.
At least the targets are...
Seung Ho has found confidence in talking.
- His confidence is back.
- He's got the confidence.
We've got to acknowledge it.
- It's only natural.
- It's only natural, really.
I'm starting to talk more quietly.
Because...
the one who already knows the guest...
- Right.
- should try to succeed.
I wanted to succeed.
(Feeling small)
The one who already knows the guest should try to succeed.
(Bull's-eye)
Good. Let's do this.
Let's try. We're all set. Let's do this.
Let's try right away.
- I have a good feeling about it.
- Okay.
Here we go.
- Ready. Set.
- Oh, dear.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
(5th try)
(A smooth start)
Jae Seok.
We might succeed.
- The time.
- All right.
We're all set.
We can do it.
- Hold on.
- One is enough.
(5th try)
- Nice.
- Okay, next.
(1 cushion foundation is left.)
(Next is Ace Seung Ho.)
I have a feeling he'll end it.
- Ten seconds left.
- Oh, no.
- It's okay. We can do it.
- I've got enough time.
- There's only one left.
- I'm finishing it.
- Okay.
- I'm finishing it!
- Of course.
Five, four...
- I'm finishing it.
- The last target.
Two, one.
(Whether they succeed or not depends on Yeon Seok's flick!)
- Oh, no.
- Gosh.
(Failed)
The time pressure is no joke.
- This itself is amazing.
- I was going to finish it.
- We had just one left.
- It was...
(Failed with 1 remaining target)
- I was going to finish it.
- This itself is amazing.
It was good. Things were great just now.
Listen.
- The first flicks were great.
- That was close.
The 3rd and 4th players must do better.
You see...
The 1st and 2nd players made a golden opportunity.
Seung Ho.
That's not how you flick it.
You've got to target it well.
How many, Young Hyun? Give him more.
- The aim matters.
- Give...
Young Hyun more.
- Do three, Young Hyun.
- Okay.
Young Hyun, do three.
- Should we each do three?
- Okay.
I'll just go with two.
(Withdrew 1 bottle cap himself)
Now then.
I'll go first this time.
- Okay. Seung Ho...
- I'll go 1st with 2 bottle caps.
- Okay.
- Good.
Were you going to flick two?
- Do three.
- I didn't say anything.
Why...
- Do three.
- Why are you...
- Okay.
Three, three, two, two.
- Seung Ho and I will do two each.
- Okay.
- Let's do this!
Let's go. I have a feeling we'll succeed.
I know, right? It's kind of...
- Just one. Let's just get one.
- Call it.
- Call it, please.
- Here I go.
- Here we go!
- Okay, here we go.
Ready. Set.
- Just 1.
- Get 1.
- Just 1, okay?
- Just 1.
Set.
(6th try)
- That was close.
- What a bummer.
- That was so close.
- So close.
How come?
Go slow.
(6th try)
- Just 1.
- Really, just 1.
- Get just 1.
- Oh, no.
- Gosh.
- Next.
- It'll close this time.
- One down.
- Nice.
- Good.
- Let me get one more.
- One more.
- That's it.
- That's it. Let's go.
- One more.
Get the last one.
(Knocked down 3 in a row)
(Yoo One Shot lived up to his name!)
Once again, I didn't do anything!
Even so, I'm so happy!
- Okay.
- It makes me happier!
Round Three,
- success!
- Success!
(They succeeded Round 3.)
The thrill is no joke.
Hold on.
- Your fingers...
- Wait.
- Does it hurt?
- I was about to hold up...
my middle finger. I was holding it up when I...
- Be careful with your fingers.
- It...
- Hold this one up.
- Nice!
The thimble was on my middle finger.
All right. With that, Mi Ri has secured...
all presents up to Round Three!
- Thank you.
- I'm in pure bliss.
- Mi Ri, congratulations.
- Thank you.
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- Thank you.
- Yoo One Shot did his share today!
Yoo One Shot.
I hit a whopping three targets.
(Yoo One Shot pulled off a big one.)
- Mi Ri, congratulations.
- I'm getting goosebumps.
We hit home runs today.
- True.
- Home Run Yoo.
- Two and three.
- Nice.
By the way,
don't you know her?
But he didn't do anything.
He did skip earlier.
It's the long friendship, right?
- Give them to her.
- Okay.
You may open it now, Mi Ri.
Her right wrist is empty.
Put it on for her.
Her accessories are...
- all on the left.
- Right?
- My left?
- Yes.
- On her right.
- Put it on her right wrist.
- How pretty.
- It's stylish.
- It's pretty.
- On her right.
- Do you mind?
- No.
- Great.
- Nice. It's pretty.
- All set!
All set! Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Good.
- Even your right is sparkly.
- Congratulations.
- Today,
we're overjoyed to have succeeded up to Round Three.
Mi Ri, thank you very much for spending...
your spare time with us.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
This feels good.
(Finished the first spare time on a happy note)
A grand slam.
- It...
- But still,
- Seung Ho played a big role today.
- For sure.
My nickname is Practice Messi.
Seung Ho is Real-deal Messi.
- Yes, Real-deal Messi.
- Real-deal Messi.
All right, it's time to move on to the second Whenever Guest.
Since it's at 12:30pm,
- we have enough time to eat lunch.
- Yes, we have two hours to spare.
- But...
- The only open restaurant is...
- that place in Cheongdam.
- The one we always go to?
- Yes.
- It's nearby.
- Or...
- Are we going to Wolfgang's?
- Wolfgang's?
- Really?
Either way, I won't lose.
If the 4 of us go, it'll cost a 100-something dollars.
It won't just be a hundred-something dollars.
We'll have to pay a thousand-something dollars.
- Will it go over like that?
- Of course.
- How much is the food?
- I pay that much for myself.
- I pay that much for a solo meal.
- Exactly.
The steak is huge.
It's expensive per gram.
Hold on, I haven't been there recently.
- How much is it?
- I won't lose anyway.
How much is the steak at Wolfgang's Steakhouse?
The price of the steak at Wolfgang's Steakhouse in Cheongdam.
The porterhouse steak is 370 dollars...
for 1,000g.
It's 370 dollars, Jae Seok.
- For two...
- They have a lunch course.
- They do.
- Do they?
- The lunch course is 130 dollars.
- Is that so?
- We can't.
- It's a no.
(It's still very pricey.)
- How...
- It's not open yet.
I see. Let's try the other side of the street first.
(They decide to walk around and look for a restaurant.)
Shall we walk around Rodeo? It's been a while.
(Laughing)
Let's take a look.
(To the alley with many must-eat places)
The area has changed a lot...
- Here?
- in the past decade.
- A lot of new buildings...
- Yes.
have been built.
Wasn't that a car wash?
(Talking about the changed Cheongdam)
- It was a car wash and...
- Right?
That's the dermatology clinic I go to.
- Where?
- Over there.
Really?
- It's all around this area.
- Exactly.
The game may be simple,
but I go all out on it.
- For real. I gave it my best.
- Right?
It was thrilling. I didn't think it would be this fun.
Walk straight, and there's Cheongdam Valley.
Or there's Yetnaljib,
- a Korean cuisine place.
- Yes. It's a Korean cuisine place.
Yes, that's another option.
Where do you want to go? Here or Cheongdam Valley?
Cheongdam Valley? I want to go there.
- Let's go.
- I've never been there.
- Okay.
- Let's grab lunch at...
Seung Ho's pick, Cheongdam Valley.
We're here.
Okay, to Cheongdam Valley.
- Welcome.
- Gosh, hi.
- Hi.
- We...
It's been ages since I've last been here.
- I haven't been here in a while.
- Right?
Yes.
What's good here?
- The Korean set meal.
I want stir-fried spicy pork.
- Stir-fried spicy pork.
- Stir-fried spicy pork is nice.
Thank you.
Do you want nurungji or white rice?
- I want the original Korean meal.
- Korean set meal.
- Korean set meal?
- Yes.
- Okay. Two Korean set meals.
- Two Korean set meals.
Two nurungji.
- One stir-fried squid.
- Okay.
One stir-fried spicy pork.
One grilled mackerel.
- All set.
- Should we get Spam?
That's too much.
(Ordering everything they craved)
- I haven't been here in ages.
- Right?
It's been over a decade since I last came here.
- I came when I was a rookie actor.
- Right?
- It was about 6 or 7 dollars.
- You're right.
My lunch budget was limited back then.
This was a great spot within my budget.
(A nostalgic space that fed him during the rookie years)
I'm glad we succeeded in Round Three.
You got to give a present to the hairstylist,
- who you used to know.
- I know.
She worked at a salon we went to early in our career.
It's been a while since we went to another one.
When I think of the days back then,
I was clueless.
And they were all experienced stylists.
When I was young,
- they were all older than me.
- They were.
At some point, the way I addressed them changed.
- How so?
- Usually,
- You were on a first-name basis.
- I called them by their names.
- And the formality kicked in.
- That's right.
- It changed.
- Things got formal.
That's when I realized how much time had passed.
When I went to a set in the past,
- the staff were older than me.
- Right.
Suddenly, I started hearing them speaking formally to me.
- I'm now older than them.
- Exactly.
- They speak formally to you.
- Yes.
- That's right.
- They treat me like an old veteran.
(Nowadays, they treat him like a veteran actor.)
You made your debut a long time ago,
- so you're a veteran actor.
- He's a veteran actor.
- Exactly.
- When did you make your debut?
- I started working in 1998.
- Goodness.
He's more experienced than I am.
(Unbelievable years of experience)
(Whopping 29 years of experience!)
- That's crazy.
- I know.
I made my debut in 2003.
- Really?
- Yes.
- He has more experience than you.
I was a clueless baby back then.
You don't remember everything in those years, do you?
Like the works.
- I can't remember everything.
- Exactly.
But I remember the ones...
- that left huge impressions.
- I see.
As you know, the atmosphere on set was...
- tough back then.
- Yes.
- It was very... Yes.
- It was the age of savagery.
Savagery...
It was the age of savagery.
It was so brutal.
They stayed up all nights...
and went through so much to film.
That's right. They didn't have that before.
Now, a child actor can work until certain hours.
- You're right.
- That's the law.
You have to send them home before midnight.
They let child actors go home before 10pm.
The shooting environment has gotten much better now.
- Yes.
- That's right.
When I shot for "Flex x Cop 2,"
it was my first time working in the environment...
that had changed in a good way.
When I shot dramas in the past,
- I used to stay up three nights.
- Yes.
So, I thought it'd be easy.
But I got exhausted...
after the shootings.
They finished shooting on time,
but I passed out after it.
- Because it's been a while.
- Yes.
People change. You get used to it quickly.
- That's how it is.
- Yes.
- Your food is here.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay. Thank you.
Here.
- Gosh. It's been a while.
- Yes. It was just like this.
- That's right.
- Goodness.
They served us a trayful of dishes.
Goodness. This is how they serve.
Gosh. They look good.
- They look tasty, right?
- Yes.
Gosh. Look.
It looks so good.
- It's been a while.
- This is it.
- This really is it.
- I'm glad we came here.
- Yes. It's been a while.
It has been so long.
Steak must've been good too, though.
(The taste of the past that is as precious as or more than steak)
- Thanks for the food.
- Please enjoy.
- Enjoy.
- Thanks for the food.
- The stew...
- We don't know who'll pay.
Let's just dig in for now.
- The table will collapse.
- You brought your cards, right?
- Yes, I brought it.
- I brought it.
- Here, Seung Ho.
- Okay. Thanks.
This is just perfect on a rainy day.
Gosh. Thank you.
The side dishes are so tasty.
(Satisfied)
(Taking a bite of good old memories)
Gosh. Hey.
It still tastes great.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
It tastes like I remember it.
I came here after an audition...
with a little bit of lingering unease.
"Hey, let's just eat for now."
- This is the taste of rookie years.
- Yes.
Yeon Shik had these during his rookie season.
It's tasty.
You're eating well, Seung Ho.
It's so good.
What's your family like? Do you have siblings?
I'm an only child.
I lived away from my parents since I graduated...
from elementary school.
I went to study abroad alone.
When I came back to be a trainee at JYP Entertainment,
they no longer needed to look after me.
They left for Canada instead.
(After he became a trainee, they moved to Canada.)
- We switched places.
- I see.
- Gosh.
- They're in Canada.
- Yes.
- You're amazing, Young Hyun.
- It's not easy to live alone.
- I've been enjoying my life.
I can't do it.
The English you learned back then...
must be so useful in your singing career.
I'm so glad about it because...
it's easier for me when I work.
- That's right.
- When I was in college,
my major was taught mainly in English.
So it helped me a lot.
- And I served as KATUSA.
- That's right.
In fact, as for DAY6,
it wasn't exactly...
- super well-known...
- Right.
- group.
- That's right.
But the old songs made it back into the charts all together.
Gosh. What a life.
- It's amazing.
- How many years...
did you spend as a lesser-known group?
"You Were Beautiful" made it back into the charts after six years...
- Exactly.
- since its release.
Because you have great songs...
and talents to support them,
when people recognized you,
- it created a synergy.
- They were ready.
- There aren't many 24-hour spots.
- Not anymore.
- They used to fill Gangnam.
- There were many.
It's because labor costs have skyrocketed.
Now...
- Eat comfortably.
- I'll eat some more.
Do you want more rice?
It's okay. This will be enough.
(The big eater is still hungry.)
(Satisfied)
(Taking another spoonful)
They all look at their phones while working on set.
(Eating with passion while even sweating)
(Taking another spoonful)
I really enjoyed it.
Order more.
It's good.
- This nurungji is good.
- Nurungji is good, right?
- It's good.
- Their nurungji is...
- I think I ate half of it.
No. You can have more.
- It's flavorful.
- Yes. It's aromatic.
(They're done with the satisfying lunch.)
- Gosh.
- That's right.
- Now, we need to pay.
- Yes. We need to play a game.
Is there a game you play with your friends?
- Any games?
- Well...
We play a ghost leg.
- A ghost leg.
- We play that.
- Let's go classic this time.
- Okay.
- Yes.
- The numbers...
It's been a really long time since I actually drew one.
- That's right.
- We're going analog.
Okay. I added more steps because it was empty.
- You have to add more at the end.
- You can't calculate the result.
Draw them comfortably.
It has to go like this.
In the end.
(Adding the final twist)
How many are you drawing?
- I gave it lots of twists.
- Now.
- Which one should we start with?
- Let's go with number one.
- Number one?
- Yes.
- Young K?
- Yes. I'll sing.
If number one gets it, the game is over.
- What?
Wait. It goes this way, right?
- Yes!
- Gosh.
Yes!
Good job, Seung Ho.
If you didn't add the line, I had to pay.
- It was good, wasn't it?
- Yes.
- Should we go in order?
- Sounds good.
- Okay. Let's go.
- Number two is Seung Ho.
I hope you get picked.
- What?
- Then you go...
- Go that way.
- Make another turn.
- It goes down and sideways.
- Yes.
It reaches here.
(Seung Ho is exempt from paying.)
It wasn't him. It's either you or me, Jae Seok.
- We're saved.
- I'll pick number four.
- Number four?
- Yes.
- Thank you for the meal, guys.
- Number four.
- Let's try number four.
- Really?
(Jae Seok is next.)
- The music is changing.
- It goes this way, right?
It's getting gloomier.
Hey. Let's survive.
Survive no matter what.
- Here it goes.
- Am I doing it right?
Am I?
- Here it goes.
- That's it.
- What?
- It's here.
- You're approaching it.
- It's you.
It's you.
(Yes. He's going for it.)
- What?
- It's here.
- Wait.
- It's you.
It's you!
(Jae Seok has to pay for this meal.)
- Thanks, Jae Seok.
- Thank you, Jae Seok.
Sure. Goodness.
- See?
- We only had Korean set meals.
- We should've gone to Wolfgang's.
- Wolfgang's Steakhouse.
We should've gone to Wolfgang's on a day like this.
We should've waited 30 minutes.
Gosh. I would've been in trouble if we had gone to the steakhouse.
Gosh. We should've gone there.
Now, I'll pay for lunch...
here at Cheongdam Valley.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Gosh. It's nothing.
No need to thank me. This is nothing.
Thank you.
- Gosh. Thanks for lunch.
- Thank you.
It was a really good lunch.
- Shall we?
- Yes.
- It's peak lunch hour.
I see a cafe on the way.
- Really?
- It's on the first floor.
What? They have sorbet and bingsu.
- Where?
- Here.
- Low-calorie desserts.
- They have everything.
- They have an Americano.
- I love it.
Let's go in.
Do we make a bet again?
Yes. Let's ask the employee to pick a card this time...
- since Jae Seok paid for lunch.
- Hello.
- They have a great selection.
They have bingsu too.
I'm going to get the classic bingsu.
- I'll get an iced Americano.
- Okay.
And one black raspberry tea, please.
And two iced Americanos.
Then I'll get the classic bingsu.
- There you go.
- We'll get two bingsus.
Please pick a card out of four cards to pay.
- You can pick whatever.
- Feel free to pick one.
Pick the one you like.
There's a fancy card.
- Don't put my card in front.
- It's the fancy card.
This is a fancy one too.
- Look.
- It's a purple one.
That card stands out.
I'm worried about the color.
- The color stands out.
- Pick anything from these four.
It's Seung Ho's card.
- Gosh. I'm saved.
- It's Seung Ho's.
Wait. She picked the most ordinary-looking card.
- They all have fancy cards, ma'am.
- Please run that card.
- Thank you.
- Others are fancy, but...
- Gosh. It's hilarious.
- They all have fancy cards.
- Yours was the same as mine.
- Oh, really?
Gosh.
Seung Ho's treating us today.
- She picked the perfect card.
- Thanks, Seung Ho.
- This place is...
- Seung Ho. It was hilarious.
"There are many fancy cards."
(Doing Seung Ho's impression)
(Staring)
I should've ordered some cookies.
A red bean brownie. They have good red beans.
It sounds tasty.
Don't you think we should try a red bean brownie, Seung Ho?
- And a carrot cake.
- I think we're good.
(He's not a pushover.)
Seung Ho has worked in the entertainment business...
for quite some time,
- so he's not to be underestimated.
- You're right.
You're good. You have to be tough.
(Getting ready to order more)
- You have to be tough, Seung Ho.
- Okay.
- A red bean brownie and...
- A red bean brownie.
- And..
- And a carrot cake.
Milk bingsu must be nice and fluffy.
You should order it since you're paying for it.
(Another dish was added.)
- You're a veteran actor.
- Sir.
- Thank you, sir.
Please order those two, sir.
- Okay.
- A milk bingsu for one person.
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay. Thank you.
- You ordered one more milk bingsu?
- Yes, I did.
Milk bingsu does sound good.
That one doesn't come with red beans.
You're right.
It's perfect if you're on a diet.
Which one?
The milk bingsu.
Did you say milk bingsu is weight-loss-friendly?
It seems low-calorie.
- They use organic sugar.
- Yes. They use organic sugar too.
Gosh. JYP Entertainment is all about organic food.
For real.
They love organic stuff.
It must be great. For lunch,
- They have organic menus.
- they serve organic food.
- Now...
- They used to be in Cheongdam.
- The small building.
- The small one.
- I'm from that building.
- Right.
Since it was in that building? That's a long time.
We're divided.
Those who were trainees at the old building.
Those who were trainees at the training center...
which was in a separate building...
- next to a movie theater.
- That's right. Right next to it.
Those who trained there.
And those who trained...
- in the new building.
- I see.
We're divided into those generations.
Our group is from Cheongdam.
(They're the 1st generation, trained in Cheongdam.)
- Yes.
- You paid for several pillars...
at the new building.
Maybe several windows.
- Window frames?
- Yes.
It's because there are great singers who came before us.
Still, the window frames on that building...
- are quite expensive.
- First of all,
- there's TWICE.
- TWICE.
They paid for the structure.
They do tours in stadiums.
Jin Young and I are...
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
Their red beans are different.
- Gosh. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you, Seung Ho.
- Yes, thank you.
She boiled the red beans herself.
(Red bean paste made from scratch)
- Gosh.
- We can have it as is.
(The highly anticipated first bite)
- Gosh. It's good.
- It's really good.
- It's soft.
- Yes.
These red beans are not too strong.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The spoons come together.)
- It's good.
- It's delicious, ma'am.
Ma'am.
(Young K's big eater mode is on.)
It's so tasty. It's milk bingsu too.
- People will line up now.
- It's amazing, ma'am.
(Devouring it as if they haven't eaten for days)
It's really good.
The rice cake on top of it is really good.
I just had one too.
It's really good.
(They can't stop eating it.)
This is worth the drive.
Gosh. We finished it.
It's gone.
It's been so long since I finished a whole bingsu.
- Gosh. It's good.
- Really.
Nice. The cab is booked.
(Navi Yoo called a cab in time.)
(But he can't let go of his spoon.)
- Gosh. Ma'am.
- We finished them.
You're eating it as if you're eating gukbap.
Gosh. He's...
- Gosh. You're really eating it.
- You're eating bingsu...
- like gukbap.
- He must love it.
(Let's go.)
- It's here.
- Let's go. It's here.
- We loved it, ma'am.
- We enjoyed it so much.
It was really good.
- Thank you.
- Bye.
- Gosh. That was good.
- That was great.
Today's lunch was amazing.
- Seriously.
- That bingsu.
Gosh. You had it as if it were a hangover soup.
It was totally my kind of bingsu.
- You had bingsu as if it were soup.
- I've never seen anyone...
eating it like that.
Maybe I ate too much of your nurungji.
- No, I had my portion of nurungji.
- You needed more food.
No.
You actually don't go around...
in a car booked for the shoot.
- No.
- I called the cab.
Exactly.
- I have to call them.
- Most of the taxi fares...
are on him.
I pay for the cabs.
And if I pay for the lunch too...
Right. You're on point.
I can understand you now.
Now, for this last one,
let's do our best.
I feel pressure.
(Intimidated)
It's because I didn't pay for lunch...
or desserts.
I never paid.
- You excelled at not paying.
- Right.
- I should do my part now.
- You're lucky.
I wonder what game we'll play.
- "Lee Ye Won."
- Ye Won.
"I'm curious about a day of our diligent princess..."
"who goes to work every day.."
- "through the morning dew."
- What?
"It's fluffy and sweet."
"It's puffy and round. We love it."
Is it a children's song?
"My daughter spends all day..."
"basking in the glow of dreams, not the sun."
"Please go see her on my behalf."
Is her daughter an employee who's working at a certain place?
She spends all day basking in the glow of dreams, not the sun.
- Is she a student?
- Exactly.
That might be right.
- Her mother sent the letter, right?
- Yes.
Round and...
- There was a song.
- "It's puffy..."
"and round. We love it."
"It's fluffy and sweet."
It's puffy and round?
- Cotton candy?
- Does she make those?
- Sticky rice cake?
- I can only think of food.
I have no idea.
What?
It's Grand InterContinental...
- It's at Parnas.
- It's Parnas.
Is it at a hotel?
What is she doing at a hotel?
Hold on. Where did you say it was?
(Where is Whenever Guest in the 5-star hotel?)
She told us to find the white hat around here.
What? Where is this place?
I think it's near there.
- Wait. They're wearing a hat.
- Right.
- They must be pastry chefs.
- There they are.
- Is she the one?
- Yes, pastry chefs.
Gosh. They're here. It's crazy.
- What?
- He's so handsome.
- Who?
- Yeon Seok's really hot.
(Those in white hats are responding transparently.)
They're staring at us. We should pretend to hang around.
- Ye Won?
- Ye Won.
- Who's Ye Won?
- Gosh.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Nice to meet you.
Right. You're wearing name tags.
- Ye Won?
- Yes.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- You must be...
- You're pastry chefs.
- That's right.
- Let's take a look at the breads.
- Shall we?
- Gosh.
(They go into the bakery without hesitation.)
Gosh. I'm a bread lover.
- Exactly.
- I love bread.
That looks good.
- Mugwort marble bread.
- Yes.
Why don't we give it a try?
- Mugwort marble bread.
- He grabbed it right away.
- Can I buy the melon bread?
- Do you have this?
(Grabbing)
- Let's pay for it first.
- Pick one.
- We should pay.
- Let's pay.
We'll pay. Choose first.
- I'll get a scone.
- Do you like scones?
(They start shopping for bread when they said they were full.)
It's a walnut cranberry bagel.
I want an egg tart.
(Giggling)
(Amazed)
- He's so tall.
- I know.
- He's taller than our hat.
- Yes.
- I love bagels.
- They're good.
I've never paid today.
Are you going to buy these breads?
Of course, I am.
It's my turn now.
There are so many tasty breads.
- Thank you.
- There are so many.
I'll pay for them all.
- Are you really buying them?
- Yes, Jae Seok.
Is Young Hyun really paying?
Wait. Whose is this?
- Mine.
- Right.
- What about this one?
- That's mine.
- This one?
I bought so much.
(Jae Seok picked 4 breads.)
- Thank you, Young Hyun.
- Yes.
- I'll enjoy them at home.
- Sure.
- This way.
- Thank you.
- Let's go now.
- Shall we?
- Let's go this way first.
- What a great course.
We bought the bread...
- from Whenever Guest's workplace.
- Yes.
This is why they go to work at 5:30am.
(They follow Whenever Guest deeper into the hotel.)
This is the staff hallway.
Is this the staff passage?
(A staff hallway appears after making many turns.)
- Gosh. This is...
- Goodness.
- It's somewhere we can't come in.
- We can't come in here.
- This is the VIP passage.
- Exactly.
- This place is really...
- It's fancy.
There must be so many staff members.
Gosh. This is it.
It's a staff lounge.
(Staff lounge)
This is the staff lounge?
Yes. We take a break here.
(A lounge designated for hotel staff to take some rest)
Are these soundproof booths?
Yes. When we make phone calls, you can't hear it.
- It's for making calls.
- Yes.
We can't hear it from the outside.
Wait. You can't really hear it?
No. We tried a few times.
Try it.
- You try it.
- Can you hear me?
- We can hear you.
- What? I can hear him.
I can hear you loud and clear.
What? Wait.
- We couldn't hear it before.
- What's going on?
- We aren't that loud.
- You can't talk loudly in there.
I didn't speak loudly.
I just said, "Can you hear me?"
- You said, "I can hear you."
- I can't believe it.
We weren't supposed to hear it.
It was so loud and clear.
- This way?
- Yes. You can sit on both sides.
Gosh. The rest of us picked one piece of bread each.
This is pathetic when I'm the oldest one.
But there were many kinds of bread that I liked.
(Amazed)
They've made a cake for us.
Gosh. That's amazing.
(Whenever Guests made these breads themselves.)
It's too precious to eat.
Gosh. It's so pretty.
Gosh. It's a mango cake.
- You shouldn't have taken us...
- Jae Seok.
to eat bingsu.
(They cleared 3 bingsus.)
- They had bingsu.
- And red bean brownie...
They love bingsu.
- Let's try the cake.
- Shall we?
Does anyone have a birthday coming up?
- A birthday.
- Birthday.
- My birthday was on the 17th.
- I see.
Happy birthday to you
(Celebrating his birthday which was 2 weeks ago...)
(since they have a cake)
(Happy)
(Throwing an unexpected birthday party for Seung Ho)
(Happy birthday to you)
- Gosh. Thank you.
- It's in August. That's right.
- Let's try it.
- Let's try it quickly.
- I want to try it.
- But it's too precious to cut it.
- I'll try it now.
- Okay.
- Please enjoy.
- Share it with Young K.
- The premium cream...
- Gosh.
tastes different.
Gosh. It has so many mango pieces.
(Satisfied)
I'm eating like a king today.
Yes, Seung Ho.
- We're eating like kings.
- Really.
Do the three of you...
play different parts?
- How does it work?
I'm responsible for cakes and buffet.
- I see.
- You made this, then.
Yes, I made it.
- She made it this morning.
- Yes.
- Did you make it this morning?
- What time?
- I prepped for it yesterday.
(It's so good.)
I made the chocolates over here.
- These?
- I see.
These chocolates.
There are four pieces.
I'm responsible for the buffet and mousse cakes.
I made the mille-feuille cake you saw upstairs.
- The fig mille-feuille.
- Yes.
- That looked good too.
- By the way,
are you all the same age?
Yu Jin and I are the same age.
Su Bin is one year older than us.
How long have you been working here?
I started working in 2021, so this is my 6th year.
- This is your sixth year.
- That's quite a while.
What about you two?
- I started next.
- And I started working.
- Su Bin is the newest one.
- Yes. I'm just the oldest one.
You're the oldest one.
- You're one year older than them.
- Yes.
(They've walked the same path toward the same dream.)
(They're more than coworkers now.)
(They're friends who support one another.)
How did you become a pastry chef, Ye Won?
When did you start dreaming of becoming one?
We all had the same reason.
(Laughing)
- There was "Yumeiro Patissiere."
- Okay.
- It was an animation.
- Yes.
Do you know it?
No, not really.
It's so famous.
- Is it?
- Yes.
(Young K knows about the animation.)
- Do you know it?
- There was a popular challenge...
where you dance along its soundtrack.
It's so famous.
(NCT WISH, THE BOYZ, TWS)
(It was a super popular challenge in 2021 joined by many idols.)
(Young K did the challenge too.)
(Thanks to the challenge, )
(the soundtrack by IU made it back to the charts.)
You gave us lots of hints.
IU sang this song.
- Yes.
- That's right.
Come to think of it...
IU must be so happy.
(He envies her.)
- Because she sang the song.
- Right.
There are animations of our time too.
Did you dream of becoming a pastry chef after watching it?
Yes.
I loved this animation when I was young.
I watched it over and over again,
thinking it would be fun to do something like that.
May I ask what your favorite kind of bread is?
It's the Hokkaido bread over here.
- I see.
- It's my favorite.
Hokkaido?
- Is this your favorite?
- Yes.
Okay. Gosh.
We did eat a lot today.
But we have to taste it.
(They have to give it a try as it's her favorite.)
Sorry. We love bread so much.
(Filling an already full stomach with cream-filled bread)
We've been eating so much nonstop.
(The big eater is fine.)
What's the cream inside?
- It's condensed milk cream.
- It's condensed milk.
- The bread itself is so soft.
- Gosh. This one.
- It must be good with coffee.
- It's perfect with an Americano.
- Yes.
- An Americano.
Which bread do you like the most, Ye Won?
I love this one.
- This one?
- Yes.
I'm sorry.
It's unfortunate.
(She likes a different one.)
We should try it a little.
- She likes this one.
- Now, Young Hyun.
- Yes.
- Seung Ho.
Yes.
Let's just try a little.
- We have to cut it well.
- They're just holding the forks.
- We did eat a lot.
- I can't do it, Jae Seok.
It's...
- He's full.
- I'm really full.
(His stomach is at capacity.)
This one is good too. It's tasty.
Your mother sent us the letter.
That's right.
My mom has never missed an episode...
since Season One of this show.
- I see.
- Yes.
She always told me...
to send a letter.
- She always said that.
- Gosh.
But I always said I was too shy to do it.
And suddenly Mom messaged me,
saying "I sent the letter."
- She wrote lots of comments...
- Really?
on YouTube before.
Did she leave many comments?
- Has she been active in this field?
- Yes.
- On Choi Hwa Jeong's channel, - Yes.
she left a comment...
with the cake I made on Christmas.
The comment said, "My daughter made this."
(She couldn't help but brag about her daughter.)
It wasn't just on our channel.
She left them on all channels.
(Her 1st fan has been active in many areas.)
She's cute.
Good.
Anyway, since we're here,
we should go for it and win presents.
- Yes.
- Gosh.
- Ye Won.
- Crack the cookie for Round One.
- Should I do it?
- Crack it open.
"The mark of the chef's hat is the trace of hard work."
"I want to cover it nicely."
"Three Polo Ralph Lauren ball caps."
(Round 1 present: 3 Polo ball caps)
- Ball caps.
- From Ralph Lauren.
- Is each of them different?
- Yes.
- We wear caps all the time.
- Look at the colors.
- They're pretty.
- I know.
The logos are different.
(Land It on the Chef’s Hat!)
(Bound a table-tennis ball...)
(and put it in the chef's hat on a head.)
(But there are only 7 table-tennis balls.)
We did it before.
We played it with Choo Sung Hoon.
- It's like that one.
- We put it in there.
It's something like that.
The next person can only go if the previous one succeeds.
Gosh. This is...
So...
- I see.
- If one fails, it's over.
This one is hard.
We have to pull it off at once.
(They all have to succeed with 7 balls.)
- Place it well on the hat.
- Isn't it too hard?
- It faces that way, right?
- I see.
There's no front and back to this hat.
- Here.
- Yes.
(Wearing the combat hat)
- Let me see. I'll look.
- Round 1 is 1 thing, but...
(Checking their looks amiably)
I don't know if we can pull through Round Three.
It won't be easy.
(Struggling alone)
The hat doesn't fit.
Unfold it carefully.
Hold on.
Why are you checking yourself out?
I have to wear the hat.
- I need to wear it properly.
- I can't believe that guy.
- It's hilarious.
- Let me wear the hat.
Sometimes, he can be really...
Let me wear it nicely.
(Checking himself out no matter what)
You didn't come here to...
I want to look pretty in it.
(Turning)
We were taking selfies.
It's like watching "Infinity Challenge."
(A sitcom is playing before their eyes.)
Gosh. This is...
Hold on.
How am I doing?
- What?
- Tilt your head.
Gosh. It doesn't work.
I did it.
You need to tilt your head down a little.
Why am I not getting it? I don't get it at all.
(It's hard to predict the landing spot...)
(because they can't see the ball.)
Gosh. It's hard.
Why am I not getting it?
(It's a total mess.)
Is it even possible for all of us to pull it off?
- I did it.
- In front?
I got it.
(It does work.)
Okay. You need to tilt your head down.
You need to tilt your head down a little.
You did it.
- It's not working at all.
- It worked this time.
(They're slowly getting the hang of it.)
- We need to tilt our heads.
- All of us have to succeed.
No.
Gosh. It's going to be tough.
Why can't I do it?
- It's not working at all.
- It worked this time.
It worked, right?
Okay.
Let's go.
What am I going to do?
(He's not getting it at all.)
Let's gather and cheer.
- Here.
- Okay.
- In 1, 2, 3, let's go!
My goodness.
When you have the ball in your hat, you can't drop it.
- We have to keep it in our hat.
- Okay.
The rest of us.
- I'll start.
- Okay. Go for it.
Say, "Here we go."
- Okay. Here we go.
- Okay.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 1.)
(1st try, Seung Ho)
- Amazing.
- Nice.
(He pulls it off on his first try in the real game.)
It's crazy.
- Nice.
- Please hold on.
That means you have a ball left.
- Give us the ball.
- Give it to me.
(They can't drop the ball until the end.)
- Okay.
- Here.
Good luck.
(1st try, Young K)
- It worked.
- He did it.
Young Hyun, hurry and sit here.
(The 2 of them pulled it off with just 2 balls!)
(What's with them?)
- Watch out.
- We have many balls left.
- Okay.
- You can't sit there.
- Isn't it here? What is this?
- Don't sit there.
You can't sit there.
- Isn't it here? What is this?
- Don't sit there. Come here.
- This way.
- What is that?
(1st try, Jae Seok)
- Let's do this!
- We have five balls left.
No, Jae Seok. It fell short.
- Was it too short?
- You have to go further forward.
- Do we have four balls now?
- I need to tilt my head down.
Yes.
- He did it.
- It worked.
- It's crazy.
- Keep going backward like that.
Okay.
(1st try, Yeon Seok)
- Put it in.
- Careful.
(They have 3 balls left.)
I think we'll succeed in Round One.
We have three balls.
- We have many balls.
- We have many chances.
- We have many balls left.
Okay.
(1st try, Yeon Seok)
- He did it.
- Gosh.
- Success.
(It went in!)
Success. Round One,
- success!
- Success!
- Okay.
- Yes.
- Good job.
- I was lucky.
- Well done.
- Good.
- Nice work.
- Good job.
- Well done.
- It wasn't bad.
- Good.
- Nice.
- You passed Round One.
Decide if you want to go for Round Two or stop.
- Go!
Let's check out the second present.
Will the number of the balls decrease?
"The unsung heroes that support us while we knead."
"Our legs need rest too."
"Three leg massagers."
(Round 2 present: 3 leg massagers)
The famous ones?
- Those work really well.
- Good.
They are the famous ones.
(3 leg massagers to give their legs some rest)
(Round 2)
(The chef's hat gets longer.)
- So that was why.
- Right.
- That was why it was short.
- I see.
That was why.
Thank you.
Hey, it got a lot longer...
- all of a sudden.
- Right.
- It feels different.
- This one...
is similar to the one you're wearing, right?
- No.
- This must be the head chef's hat.
So with more experience,
the hat must get longer.
- Right.
- It will feel harder.
This must be the head chef's hat.
- Could I use the mirror?
- Wait.
Hold on.
- Is this right for Round Two?
- Oh, come on!
Let me check.
Why are you looking for style at this moment?
Well, I have to wear it right.
There we go.
(They're taking a selfie again.)
A selfie?
Okay.
- He did it at once!
- What?
I think I've found my game.
- We should go to Round Three.
- Right.
It will feel harder.
(They start practicing in earnest.)
You shouldn't tilt your head back, Yeon Shik.
- Oh, I see.
- Right.
- Look at it until the end.
- It has to go in.
Right.
- This is what it feels like.
- Look at it until the end.
It has to go in.
(He makes it again.)
- You've found your game.
- I have.
- I've found my game.
- Right.
- Gosh.
Right. There you go.
Are you ready, Seung Ho?
This is what it feels like.
I can't get the hang of it.
You have to move in, Seung Ho.
- There you go.
- Right!
You have to move in.
They're going to make it!
- Let's go for it.
- We got this.
- Do you want to go first?
- Okay.
- You got the hang of it.
- What if I can't do it again?
This is the 1st try for Round 2.
(The talented head chef goes first.)
All right. In 1, 2, 3.
- Here we go!
(2nd try, Jae Seok)
You have to move in.
- Jae Seok got the hang of it.
- Right.
(2nd try, Jae Seok)
- He loses it in the real game.
- What happened?
It went slightly to the left.
- It was slightly off.
- To the left.
Right.
- He did it.
- It was short this time.
The bounce was short.
(The familiar face appears.)
Jae Seok.
It was short this time. The bounce was short.
(Head chef?)
- Stop using the balls.
- Hold on.
- I have to make it.
I have to make it.
- You said you got the hang of it.
- Hold on.
- Right!
- I did it.
- You did it.
- Three.
- Okay.
(2nd try, Yeon Seok)
- I have to do it in two tries.
- Don't worry about the balls.
I have to do it in two tries.
- I'll hold that for you.
- Right.
(2nd try, Yeon Seok)
Nice!
There's a sense of pressure toward the end.
- Nice.
- It's okay.
- You can do it.
- Gosh.
- Sit still.
- We have three balls left.
(2nd try, Seung Ho)
We still have a lot left.
- Hey!
- Gosh!
- All right.
- Nice!
- Step back from there.
(It's the last player now.)
- Gosh!
- Nice!
- Step back from there.
(2nd try, Young K)
- There are two balls left, right?
- Do it comfortably.
Just right there.
(2nd try, Young K)
- What?
- Awesome!
- Okay.
- Just right there.
(It went in!)
- What?
- Awesome!
- Gosh!
(They pass Round 2 in 1 go again.)
(Screaming)
- Nice!
- Awesome!
Awesome!
- Why are we so good?
- What? We did it?
- Round Two, success!
- Success!
- Gosh!
- Nice job!
- We found the perfect game.
- Things feel great today.
We found the perfect game.
- We're a great team.
- Right.
- Yes!
It's tough...
- when all four have to make it.
- It's tough.
We all have similar reflexes.
- They look a bit surprised.
- Right.
This is amazing.
- This is great.
- There are eight tries left.
- Congratulations.
You still haven't used your chance.
Please decide if you three will go or stop.
One, two, three.
- Go!
- We're going until the end!
- Things feel great right now.
"The powerful item that will save you in the morning..."
"when each second is precious."
"Dyson hair dryer."
(Round 3 present, 3 Dyson hair dryers)
- This is really powerful.
- I love it.
- I need this.
- This is really good.
- Awesome!
- Three!
- Gosh!
This is great.
It dries your hair really quickly.
(Powerful item when getting ready to go to work)
(3 Dyson hair dryers)
(Round 3)
(The number of table tennis balls gets reduced to 4.)
- Gosh.
- I knew it.
We only get one each.
- It's 1 shot, 1 kill.
It's really hard for all four of us to make it.
Gosh.
(They feel a lot more pressure with the reduced attempts.)
This is really hard.
It's hard for all of us to make it at once.
Look at it until the end.
But everyone is doing well.
It's a special day.
Nice!
(Even Yeon Seok did it at once.)
Should we go for it right away?
- Right away?
- Yes.
- Let's go for it!
- Before we feel tired.
- Let's do it before we feel tired.
- Let's do a cheer.
- Upward.
- One, two, three! Let's go!
- All right.
- Let's do this.
Seung Ho should go first since he's doing well.
- Okay. Seung Ho will go first.
- Let's go.
You two should go first.
It will be over once Seung Ho fails to make it.
- Let's go!
Let's make a miracle happen.
I'll start.
- Round Three is quite difficult.
- Here we go!
Here we go!
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 3.)
(The four were great during the actual game.)
(Will they be able to carry on with this atmosphere?)
(Letting out a sigh)
(3rd try, Seung Ho)
- He did it!
- It was like a cockscomb.
- It was like this.
- Gosh.
- He's good during the actual game.
That was amazing.
He becomes Messi during the actual game.
(3rd try, Young K)
- He's good.
- How did you do that?
You can do this, Young Hyun.
(You can do this, Young Hyun.)
Okay.
(3rd try, Young K)
- Look at it until the end.
- That was so close!
You went past it.
Failed.
(Groaning)
You went past it.
- Okay. Nice.
- That was a good try.
- We still have a lot of tries left.
- Right.
I tried to copy Seung Ho too much.
Young K has to show us something.
- It's hard for all four to make it.
- There's a certain height.
- Hold on.
(Making it)
- Gosh!
- I found it!
I found the right height.
So will you go first?
(Does he feel nervous as the first player?)
Jae Seok. We have to make it to my turn.
Right.
All right. I'll start.
"Here we go?"
- He didn't say it!
- I didn't say it!
Gosh, I didn't say it!
I asked!
- He didn't say it.
- I didn't say it!
Gosh, that would've been bad.
What's wrong with you?
- Do it with confidence.
- I got scared.
- Don't get scared.
- You have to be bold.
- I got scared.
- Be bold.
- Okay.
- It can't bounce low.
- Let's go, Messi!
- Here we go!
This is an actual try.
(Out of 10 total tries, they're on try number 5.)
Just do the same thing as you did during practice.
(5th try, Jae Seok)
- Awesome!
- He did it!
Gosh. All right.
All right.
- All right.
(5th try, Seung Ho)
(Failed)
- The hat got smaller.
- It's okay.
- Hold on.
- When...
- The top part got smaller.
- Right.
It's because you have such a small head.
There we go. This makes it much better.
- Can I have a cup of water?
- Yes.
This is crazy.
The chance hasn't been used yet.
It's 6, 7, 8, 9, and 10.
There are five tries left.
- I think Seung Ho should do first.
- Right.
- Seung Ho should go 1st.
- He did well as a 1st player.
- Done.
- Right.
- Let's do this.
- Let's do a cheer.
Let's do a cheer.
- All right.
- Us as well?
- In, 1, 2, 3. Let's go!
Let's do this.
- Just like during practice.
- I'll start.
- Let's go!
- All right.
- Here we go!
Let's do this.
(Seung Ho is good during the actual game.)
(6th try, Seung Ho)
It went in!
- Shouldn't this count?
- Why?
Shouldn't this count?
Why? What happened?
- It bounced back out.
- I threw it too hard.
- Gosh.
But it went in.
We have four tries left.
We lose our tries really quickly.
When the four of us have to make it at once...
- It's really hard.
- We lose our tries quickly.
- Right.
- That's what happens.
This is what happens when we pass...
- the 1st 2 rounds quickly.
- You're right.
- Let's go!
Practice a bit, Seung Ho.
- Right.
- It's too low right now.
It's too low.
- Hold on. What's wrong with me?
- It has to bounce a bit higher.
- Right.
- What number do you want?
There you go.
That was it!
You have to throw it with confidence.
- Overcome it through practice.
- Hey, Young K.
That's great, Young K.
- Overcome it through practice.
- Hey, Seung Ho!
Overcome it through practice.
(He makes it consecutively.)
Gosh, he made it every time.
(The ball goes in every time.)
I just did it ten times in a row.
- I did it ten times in a row.
- Gosh!
- They're so good.
We need to do it just like during practice.
- Here we go!
- Let's go!
- Seung Ho is covered in sweat.
(Breaking out in a cold sweat)
- Here we go!
- Let's do this.
Just like during practice.
(7th try, Yeon Seok)
- He did it.
- Nice!
- He did it!
- Nice. Stay right there.
Nice. Stay right there.
- Do you want to go next?
- You should go.
I'm feeling pressure all of a sudden.
- Okay.
- Right.
(They change the order.)
(Regretting it quickly)
We failed to go past the second player.
Do it just like during practice.
Feel comfortable. We did great during practice.
(7th try, Jae Seok)
- I did it!
- He did it!
(Jae Seok makes it as well.)
(There are two players left.)
Should I go first?
- What?
- Should I go first?
Do you want to go next? What should we do?
Do you want to go next? Should I go?
- What should we do?
- Gosh, it's hot.
- You don't want your turn to come.
- Seung Ho.
Let's go, Seung Ho.
- I'll go next.
- Okay.
- Finish it up for us.
- Remember the same feel.
- Gosh, it's hot.
Do what you did just now.
Let's end it.
(7th try, Seung Ho)
This is a great chance.
- He didn't start.
- He was practicing.
- He bounced it.
- He likes dancing!
Failed.
(They failed on their seventh try.)
Seung Ho likes dancing!
- He bounced the ball.
- Right.
He bounced the ball.
- "How high will it go up?"
- You bounced the ball, right?
- That's what he checked for.
- Right.
- You...
- He bounced it.
- Right.
He looks completely out of it.
Hey, Seung Ho.
You look out of confidence with your throw.
- Is this too hard for you?
- I can't do this!
He's too nervous!
I can't do this! I'm terrible at these things!
You're great during practice!
(He never felt this kind of pressure.)
Let's try one more time.
- Gosh.
- Let's try one more time.
- Chance?
- Chance.
- Right.
- They called it out.
- Great.
- Gosh.
Ye Won.
(They use the chance for a change in atmosphere.)
All right. Open it up.
(What kind of chance did the Whenever Guest pick?)
- There will be a bad one as well.
- Gosh!
- It's the lucky one!
- What is it?
- "The ace does it alone."
- The ace does four alone?
- Four alone?
- Gosh.
Four alone?
- But...
- Well,
no one is exceptional among us.
It just needs to be four, doesn't it?
(Young K starts practicing right away.)
(Making it once)
(Making it twice)
(Making it 3 times)
- Young K is so good.
- Right.
Would you like to give it a try, Young Hyun?
- You should do this, Young Hyun.
It's time for you to show who you are.
But this doesn't reduce our number of tries, right?
- It does.
- It shouldn't get reduced.
It shouldn't get reduced.
- You should go, Young Hyun.
- Come on!
- It shouldn't get reduced.
- Right.
Why are their backs all wet?
Come on!
I think that side has better luck.
- Right.
He did it ten times in a row over there.
He does it well on that side.
- Nice.
- That side has better luck!
You got the hang of it.
- Right!
- That's it!
(He found the perfect spot.)
- You'll do it ten times in a row!
- That's it!
- Hey!
- Hey, stay right there.
- Keep that same feeling.
- Go for it right away.
- Done.
- Go for it!
- Here.
- I'll give you the balls.
- Go for it.
- Call out, "Here I go."
- Call it out.
Go to the middle.
- No! This is the lucky spot.
- Oh, right.
- Okay.
- Let's go!
In 1, 2, 3.
- Call it out.
- Are you going to start?
- Yes.
- You have to call it out first.
- Here I go!
- You're okay, right?
Here I go!
Do it with confidence.
(They're already on their ninth try.)
- Please!
- Nice.
Don't feel any pressure.
- Here I go!
- Do it with confidence.
(9th try, Young K)
Failed.
- Failed.
- Why did you throw it there?
Young Hyun! Hold on.
(They failed with the chance.)
I could already tell.
He looked lost when he called out, "Here I go."
His eyes went blank.
He looked completely lost.
Why did you throw it here?
- Gosh.
- Why do that all of a sudden?
Gosh, this is crazy.
- This is really hard.
- I'm not sure.
- Gosh.
- This is what happens.
This is what happens when you lose the pace.
It's the last try?
(They end up reaching the last try.)
(Sweating buckets)
What happens now?
(Making it during this try is the only solution.)
Let's keep the order like this.
- Right.
- One, two, three, and four.
- Right. That sounds good.
- Right.
Let's do one last cheer!
(Last try)
All right.
- I feel so nervous.
- The last cheer!
- All right.
- Please!
Please!
In 1, 2, 3.
- Let's go!
Let's do it with confidence.
Oh, gosh.
- We can do this.
- I'll start.
- All right. Here we go.
Be bold.
(There's only one try left.)
Gosh, I can't speak.
- Seung Ho.
- What do I do?
I can't call out, "Here we go."
It's okay.
- It's okay. You can do this.
- I also feel nervous.
- You can do this.
You can do this, Seung Ho.
- It's okay.
- You did well during practice.
- You're better than me, Seung Ho.
- Do the same thing with confidence.
- You did well.
- Do it with confidence.
All right. Let's go!
I just realized this.
We didn't have the balls in our hands.
- Right.
- That made us feel anxious.
- It made us think...
- that there were no balls left?
- Right.
It made us think that there were no balls left.
- I'll keep the balls in my hands.
- Let's go!
- All right.
- Feel comfortable.
- Here we go.
- Right.
(He finally called out, "Here we go.")
- I'll just go for it.
- Right.
Just go for it.
Make a bold throw.
Be bold.
(This is the last chance!)
Just go for it.
Make a bold throw.
(Last try, Seung Ho)
(Game over)
(The last try ends right away.)
(He returns the table tennis balls.)
(In despair)
- Gosh!
- We didn't see that.
- They're taking them back.
- Right.
Well,
there's a great sense of nervousness that comes during the last try.
No one will know how it feels without giving it a try.
- It was really hard.
- Right.
We're very disappointed about failing.
It feels different during the actual game.
- Right.
- It feels...
There was only one try each.
(He makes it though it's a bit late.)
I did it so easily.
Once the game begins...
(Sweating buckets)
Every second must've felt precious...
- for you.
- It's fine.
- Thank you.
- One of them has a clock.
- Gosh!
Thank you.
- Let's carry them.
- Let's place this in the kitchen.
Let's carry them.
- My gosh.
- It's okay.
I know what it feels like.
I've never seen Seung Ho look this nervous.
He has over 28 years of experience.
Gosh, it was the same with Young Hyun.
- It makes you lose control. Right.
- I broke down.
I broke down.
We feel terrible.
No. It's fine.
- I feel terrible right now.
- Don't feel that way.
I can't look at them.
- I'm struggling to look at them.
- Gosh, how disappointing.
(In Incheon...)
(The same street...)
(feels different the next day.)
(There's an amazing legend.)
(There's a market over there.)
(People fought with cabbages and radishes.)
(That's Incheon.)
(The very competitive gambler, Byun Yo Han)
(Here I go! I'll go for it.)
(Betting without hesitation)
(Stop practicing!)
(Let's take away his!)
(Yo Han!)
(He won't allow anything that goes against his flow.)
Yo Han...
(He's the most competitive one we've met!)
(Another one who is competitive like Yo Han)
(The gambler in petty games, Roh Jae Won)
(Here I go!)
(Due to his strange sounds, )
(Gambler Roh gets teased.)
(Making...)
(consecutive mistakes)
(Where has the true gamer gone?)
(I came to Korea yesterday.)
(After sharing about how they have been, )
(they talk about many different things.)
(The Incheon talk...)
(is endless.)
(The two won't step on the brakes.)
(These two were chatters.)
(Along with Incheon's two gamblers, )
(they go all in without looking back!)
(Whenever Possible Season 5)